[
  {
    "question": "A motivation factor is how much we value something we #blank#.",
    "answer": "teach",
    "id": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "A #blank# relationship with the teacher benefits children in so many ways.",
    "answer": "positive",
    "id": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motivation is influenced by whether students judge if they can be #blank# with a task",
    "answer": "successful",
    "id": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a child seems #blank# then one question to ask is whether they have experienced success.",
    "answer": "unmotivated",
    "id": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Positive feedback builds #blank# and is very effective teaching tool.",
    "answer": "relationships",
    "id": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "No matter what happens, we should always do our best to treat children with #blank#",
    "answer": "respect",
    "id": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Children #blank# the way we treat others.",
    "answer": "watch",
    "id": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "For each agreement there is a #blank# language.",
    "answer": "sign",
    "id": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pre-corrections help children be #blank#!",
    "answer": "successful",
    "id": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before you #blank# teaching something to children, be sure to get their attention.",
    "answer": "Start",
    "id": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reinforce #blank# of positive behaviour throughout the class time.",
    "answer": "expectations",
    "id": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "One effective way to learn material is to #blank# it to someone else.",
    "answer": "teach",
    "id": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "During discussions #blank# learn communicational skills.",
    "answer": "students",
    "id": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students love to play games and solve #blank# puzzles",
    "answer": "solve",
    "id": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Graphic organisers capture #blank# of a theme",
    "answer": "essence",
    "id": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Music and #blank# are much loved activities in the class",
    "answer": "movement",
    "id": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "The teacher #blank# and student workbooks offer numerous teaching ideas",
    "answer": "manuals",
    "id": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is helpful to tie the learning as #blank# as possible to the concepts to be taught",
    "answer": "closely",
    "id": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Partner activities and #blank# are beneficial",
    "answer": "solve",
    "id": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "When planning,focus on the learning outcomes for each #blank#",
    "answer": "lesson",
    "id": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Check for #blank# and review the important concepts with childern",
    "answer": "understanding",
    "id": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students #blank# for ten minutes at the beginning of the school day.",
    "answer": "meditate",
    "id": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "Introspection focuses our attention on the #blank# of our behaviour.",
    "answer": "patterns",
    "id": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "While meditating we can experience the #blank# of our soul.",
    "answer": "peace",
    "id": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "The meditation instructions can be found at the back of every #blank# manual",
    "answer": "teacher",
    "id": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Introspection helps us develop #blank# qualities.",
    "answer": "ethical",
    "id": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students acquire peace #blank# techniques.",
    "answer": "building",
    "id": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "We can understand the #blank# of our soul.",
    "answer": "nature",
    "id": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students learn how to live #blank# life.",
    "answer": "balanced",
    "id": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "Peace #blank# with me.",
    "answer": "begins",
    "id": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students study the #blank# of peace builders.",
    "answer": "lives",
    "id": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Listening is a #blank# tool to get along with others.",
    "answer": "communication",
    "id": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students #blank# different careers in the communication field.",
    "answer": "explore",
    "id": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students explore the reasons why people choose a #blank# diet.",
    "answer": "vegetarian",
    "id": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students can do a #blank# of their own personal choice.",
    "answer": "project",
    "id": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students learn to apply their #blank# help people in need.",
    "answer": "knowledge",
    "id": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "They work together to achieve a #blank# goal.",
    "answer": "common",
    "id": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students express their own spiritual ideas creatively through various #blank# forms.",
    "answer": "art",
    "id": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "They learn about the dangers of #blank# and drugs.",
    "answer": "alocohol",
    "id": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": " times when a #blank# test is important.",
    "answer": "written",
    "id": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assessing whether students have met the #blank# of the lesson is important.",
    "answer": "goal",
    "id": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students can be asked to #blank# on their own behaviour.",
    "answer": "reflect",
    "id": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students #blank# to set goals.",
    "answer": "learn",
    "id": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are #blank# for each grade level.",
    "answer": "blueprints",
    "id": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enrichment #blank# are mentioned in the yearly syllabus.",
    "answer": "activities",
    "id": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "They learn about the dangers of #blank# and drugs.",
    "answer": "alocohol",
    "id": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "The impact of the Spiritual Curriculum can be #blank# throughout the year.",
    "answer": "observed",
    "id": "47"
  },
  {
    "question": "A motivation factor is how much we value something we #blank#.",
    "answer": "teach",
    "id": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "A #blank# relationship with the teacher benefits children in so many ways.",
    "answer": "positive",
    "id": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motivation is influenced by whether students judge if they can be #blank# with a task.",
    "answer": "successful",
    "id": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a child seems #blank# then one question to ask is whether they have experienced success.",
    "answer": "unmotiviated",
    "id": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "Positive feedback builds  #blank#  and is a very effective teaching tool. ",
    "answer": "relationships",
    "id": "52"
  },
  {
    "question": "No matter what happens, we should always do our best to treat children with #blank#.",
    "answer": "respect",
    "id": "53"
  },
  {
    "question": "Children #blank# the way we treat others. ",
    "answer": "watch",
    "id": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "One effective way to learn material is to #blank# it to someone else. ",
    "answer": "teach",
    "id": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "During discussions #blank# learn communication skills.",
    "answer": "students",
    "id": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "Students love to play games and #blank# puzzles.",
    "answer": "solve",
    "id": "57"
  },
  {
    "question": "Graphic organisers capture the #blank# of a theme.",
    "answer": "essence",
    "id": "58"  
  },
  {
    "question": "Music and #blank# are much loved activities in the class.",
    "answer": "movement",
    "id": "59"
  },
  {
    "question": "For each agreement there is a #blank# language.",
    "answer": "sign",
    "id": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pre-corrections help children be #blank# ! ",
    "answer": "successful",
    "id": "61"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before you #blank# teaching something to children, be sure to get their attention.",
    "answer": "start",
    "id": "62"
  },
  {
    "question": "The teacher #blank# and student workbooks offer numerous teaching ideas.",
    "answer": "manual",
    "id": "63"  
  },
  {
    "question": "It is helpful to tie the learning as #blank# as possible to the concepts to be taught.",
    "answer": "closely",
    "id": "64"  
  },
  {
    "question": "Partner activities and #blank# are beneficial.",
    "answer": " discussions",
    "id": "65"  
  },
  {
    "question": "When planning, focus on the learning outcomes for each #blank#.",
    "answer": "lesson",
    "id": "66"  
  },
  {
    "question": "Check for #blank# and review the important concepts with children.",
    "answer": "understanding",
    "id": "67"  
  }
]